{
    "subject": "resource/Allisyn_Ashley_Arm",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Allisyn Ashley Arm (born April 25, 1996) is an American actress and sketch comedian. Arm is most known for her main role as Zora Lancaster on Sonny with a Chance and in Disney Channel's sketch comedy series So Random!",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Allisyn Ashley Arm is: Allisyn Ashley Arm (born April 25, 1996) is an American actress and sketch comedian. Arm is most known for her main role as Zora Lancaster on Sonny with a Chance and in Disney Channel's sketch comedy series So Random!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9163196086883545,
            "question": "Name one of the sketch comedy series starring Allisyn Ashley Arm."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151102304458618,
            "question": "In which television series did Allisyn Ashley Arm play Zora Lancaster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.881729245185852,
            "question": "When was Allisyn Ashley Arm born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8526298999786377,
            "question": "What is Allisyn Ashley Arm best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8461973071098328,
            "question": "Is Allisyn Ashley Arm known for acting or stand-up comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389779329299927,
            "question": "What Disney Channel show featured Allisyn Ashley Arm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7578043341636658,
            "question": "What profession does Allisyn Ashley Arm have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7363496422767639,
            "question": "What is Allisyn Ashley Arm's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7260615825653076,
            "question": "What year did Allisyn Ashley Arm start her career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6634037494659424,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other talent does Allisyn Ashley Arm possess?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Allisyn Ashley Arm is: Allisyn Ashley Arm (born April 25, 1996) is an American actress and sketch comedian. Arm is most known for her main role as Zora Lancaster on Sonny with a Chance and in Disney Channel's sketch comedy series So Random!",
            "html": "dbpedia_7223_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Allisyn Ashley Arm start her career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7223_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Allisyn Ashley Arm's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7223_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Allisyn Ashley Arm have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7223_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7223_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text about Allisyn Ashley Arm directly states that she is an American actress known for her roles in \"Sonny with a Chance\" and \"So Random!\".  This aligns with the given comment. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention Allisyn Ashley Arm as an American actress and sketch comedian, with her main role being Zora Lancaster on Sonny with a Chance and in Disney Channel's sketch comedy series So Random!. Therefore, the information in the documents supports this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response indicates that the provided comment about Allisyn Ashley Arm is supported by the documents, as they mention her roles in \"Sonny with a Chance\" and \"So Random!\", which aligns with the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}